[music]
he managed to go beyond the Chinese
confucius to achieve a sense of freedom in the
track in
1985 his main slogan was to
stay on top without forgetting
about self-defense
[music]
[applause]
Long Mon Tabo is sneaky
[music]
dragon the film starred Pong Shun Chan
Wing Lin and others
[music]
[applause]
ye
[music]
[applause] [music] [
applause]
[music]
[applause]
You make a conscious decision to
marry in this country and bear
full responsibility for it our
state is always favorable to
lovers Now you must be faithful to
each other bride  becomes a wife
for only one
person Let's pray before
our Lord And ask him to
bless the
newlyweds So that evil stays as far away from them as
possible So that they are protected from envy of
someone else's happiness So that they can
build their
own So that they do not treat
each other and
others with arrogance So that they do not publicly
insult each other and
others The only way to achieve
goodness and mutual understanding is to marry this
couple Because for a man, a family is a castle And
for a wife, it's a yard But don't be like me
Be who you think you need to be
To achieve happiness I hope you have found your
true match and are ready for
marriage I am sure your feelings are
sincere After all, you prove them before the
Lord Do you swear that you will
protect Her and respect her until death do
you part Well, of course I have already
spent so much money on her
[music]
bride Do you swear to love the man
you have chosen as your
husband To belong to him and satisfy his
needs until death do you part
I swear
[music]
tie
dong-dong  tie
[applause]
[music]
nnnnn wait a
minute do you want to marry her
I would be very
[music]
glad And you want to marry
him great hurry up if you want to
marry each other And what will happen to
you don't worry I'm not
[music]
working here it's not a space as a priest on a
permanent
basis it's time to quit being a
priest and helping
others I'm tired of constantly listening to
some advice from you Maybe it's time to
move up the career
ladder I still can't find
any job I think it's time for me to
go to
Thailand and wouldn't you like to
join a martial
arts competition it's not interesting at all
Hello, Mr. Chin Let's
get acquainted Well, so you've
met And now let me
introduce you to our staff
gardener janitor driver cook
maid teacher this is our nanny this is
our future Pash
Governess Good day to all of you Now
I'll work here as a guard although you
can call me a bodyguard here's another
dream to yourself good  Your job is to
raise the alarm if something happens And
you have T dessert after tea is given what
tea Piti But this is us Now we will figure out who
started such rumors we need to find out rumors
exactly rumors Damned rumors answer
Who said this Who is
this vandal answer Well what
reputation who is this person Well
maybe it is our quartermaster well we will
check your version from the waist I wet myself I
will tell this person is over 40 okay with
this enemy we will figure it out for you there is one more
condition learn it Not too many
conditions but Tell me under no circumstances
should you fall in love with the owner's daughter what do we
do when we see her we follow her with our eyes
her room is upstairs and no one should under any
circumstances go there Remember
this And who are you
we are going to clean the rooms go
as you understand it does not
concern them is it too strict with you here
a lot of you
know in Hong Kong of course there are plenty of
girls but only she is a virgin in Hong Kong
got it
and you are sure of it
How dare you not  get mad at him
he's certainly a rude guy and he'll get it for it
[music]
dad don't move we have your
daughter We demand a ransom for her 5 mil on your
knees I'll pay everything wait
I'm in a tough spot right now I don't have
much money Why don't we come to an
agreement Maybe they'll haggle they'll give you a
discount Damn
you all What are you talking about
if my daughter was taken hostage I'd
pay 10 million you're all scumbags and scoundrels
useless creatures all of you And
you've been crawling on your knees your whole life
Well, that's enough of this circus, buddy,
who of us is putting on a circus here Just
look at them you don't look like
bandits at all what kind of masks are these what are
they hiding what
age are you at all it's not too early to become a criminal you probably have
n't played enough yet And this one
wears glasses Why did you go to work wearing glasses And
if I hit you, why are you laughing They
didn't teach you to call for help when you're in
danger, help me
[music] [
applause]
[music]
[applause]
ah
[music]
[applause]
[music] [
applause]
y
[music]
[applause]
ah
[music]
[applause]
Ja
[music]
[applause] [music] [
music] [applause
]
H
[applause] [music]
[applause] [music] [
applause] [music] [
applause]
[music]
great
job
excellent Yeah
great What are you
hiding there for I'm here to report the
danger Come down quickly dad now I'll
ask for more in exchange for her life 10
million bucks drive quickly or you'll get a
corpse jump
[music]
Quickly you're okay Okay
move us apart
Quickly dad But he's the one
I know when to reward And when to
punish No  Intervene
Never owe anyone anything I will
of course offer a reward but I need to
count the damages for beating people
100,000 for damaged furniture 180,000 for
damaged TV 10,000 got up for the
owner's daughter 100,000 Total You owe
us
390 And the amount will change if I hit you
Well that's it
Goodbye But if you leave you
will be unemployed again I will become unemployed this does
not mean that I will die of
hunger Dad well don't just stand there like a pillar he
saved me But he left himself I didn't kick him
out remember you wanted to help me
become an
actress Maybe you can help him too I think he
will succeed Okay I need to get
him back Just keep in mind don't try to pester her
[music]
can you
help me I want a Chinese
steak something like this what happened
Listen you smart guy Let me go How
dare you How dare you make a move on my
man
where is
Tolon Otherwise we  let's smash your
[music]
[laughter]
cafe to hell You have excellent muscles Be
careful
[laughter]
So Who's here
tons of this
Money wants to be our
roof Listen and this is not bad very well filmed
Well, how's it going Not bad and now
Call the stuntman stuntman Where are you
ready what emotion should I play
director forget about the
face we're not going to film you're just
going to beat her in the frame cameraman
ready let's start now Where's my
pipe ready Well, cameraman,
okay, mister director, what's the matter it
seems to me these clothes don't fit but
according to the script you have to wear this What did you
expect Didn't you read the script it's
mentioned several times you'll have to
wear this the whole
movie be
patient sit
down sit down Well, what's ready, okay,
camera Stop making noise, shut up, it's the
only noise here,
it's quiet
[laughter]
you're doing the best you can
Now crawl between my
legs
quickly
filmed Let's use a stuntman in this scene
I'm the director here and not you
understand Don't forget this is your first time cutting
here so that  help you Okay, okay,
just don't embarrass me in public let's call a stuntman stuntman
Where are you There he is
[laughter]
[music]
[applause] Are
you crazy or where is the camera working
we still have to sell this film to America
My father is not an
American ours The boss is from
Hong Kong What is your name Long Tai What a
stupid name Okay, let's
listen I'm already A little late I
need to go to another shoot Let's
solve this problem somehow Okay,
cameraman Shoot a few close-ups with him
then we'll insert them during editing Thank you
very much You're welcome good luck on the
set cameraman here
[music]
Well
[laughter] come on come on come on
Who's next
[music]
[applause] filmed filmed like that
assistant
director What the hell are you doing I
told you not to tire out the lead actors
Why don't you use stunt doubles
come here come here
I'll tell you something It's to
save money they'll have to pay less later I
understand what  Railway
chair our main actor smoke Would you
like your tea
sir maybe
a towel like this Bring the camera here a little
more naked will help us
earn more on the
film like this much better come on
tense up here
[music]
so ready Camera Action [
music]
[applause]
[music]
no
producer come here Where did you get these
idiots They are behaving stupidly There is simply
nowhere Do you really think that I will
continue filming 3000 for this is not
good we will share the profits with you
mister director ok so be it But
next time warn me Listen you will
sit down now no lie down actually
I have a name the director can call you
whatever he wants you are 5 per day in platt I
like it go away I can call you whatever I
want I understand
action don't film this Let it be just like that
stronger
[music]
this time he appointed me as
director there will be a free place we will take
you somewhere  let's take it I'll
pay him back at the same time Listen, are you telling everyone this?
Stop it, mister director, maybe you don't
need so many fight scenes. The more
the better, the easier it will be for the editor I know
how much we pay for the film. Get lost, I
heard him. Get lost,
director, you're not going too far. I'll
tell dad everything, I understand, so that he doesn't
pick on anyone, especially him. I understand. What's
next in the
script, you see, I
can also be a director, even an assistant director, doesn't
know anything, in the next scene, the actress
kisses our
hero, don't interfere here, stuntman. We don't need you now.
Your earnings for
today go, but 20%. You have to give me
these are the rules. When you need us again,
we'll
call you. This scene needs to be filmed in one
take. Let's get started.
[music]
[applause]
mister director. How did
you do such a scene? We didn't have one. It was
only added now. We'll re-film it. No,
no, we don't. The audience will
forgive us. How dare he hang around
my daughter. Don't take your eyes off her.  Listen
[music]
Youth is like
fire it's full of hope and
passion Only you and I in this
world strive to achieve fearlessness
[music]
but Everything around us is confusing and makes it hard to tell
right from wrong but we
develop a sense of
justice knowing that evil
exists in this
[music]
world we feel
oppressed 'Cause that's
life but we would never
give up no matter what life is
we will fight
forever
[music]
eternity is like
fire
grow Only you and I in this
world strive to achieve
fearlessness but Everything around us is confusing
and makes it hard to tell right from wrong
[music]
but we develop a sense of
justice knowing that evil
exists in this
world we feel
[music]
oppressed 'Cause that's
life but we would never
give up no matter what life is
we will fight
forever forever
[music]
and we will not be defeated no matter what
life is we will
fight we will fight forever
[music]
We must talk to
Mr. Chen he is my father do you want to
so that we could just run away
[laughter]
buddy Do you like your
job What job are you talking about with your
talents you can be anyone you are
smart strong young and brave you are wise You have a
great sense of humor you are a very
nice and neat young
man it feels like you are talking about
Prince Charles
And why not it
seems like the reason I am not here I
want to tell you something first
listen In view of how much you have
done for the
company I am giving you a trip to Thailand
for one month
[applause]
[music]
this is a
misunderstanding a
misunderstanding the fact is that he won the
fight another fact is that I lost 50,000 and
all responsibility for this lies with you
now You owe me this is not a
small amount they are trying to blame you For what reason
so I
think you do not want to be
scapegoats Besides you promised to give him to
me and I in turn guaranteed
him success it turns out you did not fulfill
your
conditions And I am wondering Which
boxer is he now it is easier to invest
more money in another
boxer and he will defeat your  with his
eyes closed ours couldn't even say a word after that
And you should have paid
attention none of this would have happened I
hope you've
finished the conversation is
continuing Yes
Of course we'll continue the
negotiations I hope she's speaking on your
behalf Yes
Of course then I would ask you to
get out of here and
go Or tell her not to interfere I heard
Don't interfere when I
speak the truth Besides,
you're no longer capable of settling such issues
it's not your fault at all the fault of
what I'm guilty of that the first time I gave
him to you and when he lost for you it's my fault
when he won the
last time I didn't send anyone to
protect him and still you lost many
of your hired killers it's also my fault
and the fact that he could have died because of you it's
not your
fault it's you who tried to kill him
with your dirty tricks How did you
have the courage to do such a thing I want
you to do something Usik We're going to
make a lot of money and we can split
it 80 to 100% the
fact that I treated him badly before
it's not true I even gave him a large
sum for current expenses not  believe me
ask him he was never
dissatisfied either
maybe we'll split the money
equally last time because of the division of money
our people were accidentally killed a
real usurer you kill
set up and help money and as for
your profit you won't miss out
you are a wolf in sheep's clothing this is slander
why do that I'm sorry but I won't
stay here you are an ungrateful bastard I'm
going too brother So two
[music]
murderers left you Well then go away again [music] [
laughter]
[music] let's
see what you say let's see
[applause]
S
[music]
a [music]
Bobby Okay I admit defeat what do you
need you lost but let's agree
what do you mean you understood everything correctly let's
organize a loss in a jiffy
Definitely he is now a
success to one we'll split the profit you know what you
Take the money and I need something
else I want to take part in
organizing the next
hand competitions  Bring me some
wine you want me to be a loser so
I'll tell you for free
why in Thailand I have to be
under someone's
control I achieved everything myself I
practiced And kept myself in shape
While they force me to accept the
conditions all this time I fought with all my
might breaking bones
damaging I can endure anything But I
wonder how you're going to make
me accept their
conditions How long do you think I'll have to
perform in the
ring I've always dreamed of becoming a champion Well
I'm just a clown
you won't be a clown If you don't consider yourself as one
no I'm a
clown who just entertains these
players no one knows about my
abilities I
know I found you and led you to success from the
very bottom to instantly turn
me from a champion into a loser because of
some bets But you're not the same anymore What you
were 3 years ago you became better 3
years these 3 years should have been
enough to save me from something
like this save me from
what
quit you also know that This is the price of
changing places of
performance you started to fight on  in the
backwoods
or to win And now it won't work
because it's money that decides it's an
integral part of performing on the
big Rings you're still performing
on the Rings the only difference is that before
you were unknown Now you've become
famous and more ambitious So
now you'll have to think about the bets that are
made on you and don't blame yourself for it
Be
smarter act like a child such
behavior is unworthy for you the
contract will end after
all the competitions are over After all
this I will make you a champion I'm not a
champion but I have ambitions and
aspirations I don't want to be
controlled by anyone again if that's necessary you
can fight instead of
me Let me give you one piece of
advice To achieve something I
suggest you go for a
while in
this will do you good there is no place for
dreams there is only harsh reality
there only the winner survives and don't
think that I want you to lose and not
become a champion this is not so all the
circumstances I owe Bobby so I
can't go any other way you will lose the fight
but you will find freedom without this the
Freedom that you  wish you not to
find, you can of course not fight
on the street at all or you will still help me, otherwise
your only way out is to look for
students, and if you don’t find them, you will become a
hermit until you die in an embrace with
alcohol and prostitutes, but if I were
you, I would not
[applause] [applause]
retreat, but
[applause]
brother, it’s me, Long Tai, I’m here, I came
to Thailand to see you, be careful.
I came here to
see the sights. I’ve been looking for you since I
got off the plane. I saw how
this guy fights and he’s much weaker than
you. And I also noticed how that chick is
staring at you, specifically at
you, is she your
fan, brother. Well, what did I guess?
Where are you dragging me? This is my older
brother. I just wanted to talk. I’m rooting
for him. Brother, you simply must
win. Dodge his
blows. Look, his lip is split. Hit him.
Come on, faster. Pay
attention. You need to constantly strike.
Why are you retreating so suddenly
and hit back Be careful that he does
n't catch you on the
attack What do you
need And what ca
n't you shout about? Come on brother,
forward, beat your son Let's stab him to death
so that he can defeat you The main thing is to take care of your
head
[music] [applause] y [music] [music
]
[applause]
[music]
ah oh
[applause]
Well, what did they say about
it They said you don't keep your
word By the way, they're not the only ones who say
that There are traitors among us
Then I'll ask you Guys, are you
for or against me
I know that our mission is very dangerous
Let's do this Those who are
not going to follow
me Take a step
forward then Those who don't support me
should take a step back So that no
one has moved away
Listen carefully tomorrow we're heading into the
jungle I see But
why do I know what you're
thinking You think how can we escape
from Bobby's people At the airport Mom port or
at the bus station we'll split up so that they
don't catch us  noticed Of course we ca
n't hide forever
maybe At first it will be a little
difficult but this problem is quite
solvable in crowded places Bobby won't dare
touch us for this don't
worry but they
definitely won't let us go unpunished When I finish all the
business here I will gather you all but this is a
God-forsaken place Besides there are all
sorts of cannibals there don't
worry even though they are
savages in no way compared to Bobby they do
n't go with them it will be much easier to
deal with but they are absolutely
ruthless Besides we do
n't know anything about this jungle Calm down I
will contact my half-sister She will
help us I don't think she will refuse
[music]
Who is there Long
Tai I came to you because I couldn't find
my
brother he must have gone to look for Bobby
come with me
[music]
n We didn't promise to go with him Those who don't
want to go take a step
back everyone took a step back it means
we shouldn't go moreover by doing so you have
proven that you support me  no
later Or time to negotiate
[laughter]
I want to fight you
maybe the results of the competition depend
on
you But don't you dare drag my
brother into this [ __ ] I don't want to lose
face Besides my people That died in vain
too
late But you can't deny it
once I fought for your
well-being and great fortune
Okay I'll help you
enjoy the
fight of course that's if you can
win
[music]
him win him and you can refuse the
contract But we'll still remain
good friends
[laughter]
[music]
[music] be
careful be careful turn away from
his punches he has strong punches
[music]
enough Just dodge
Attack I say Attack And you
relax as if I asked you to
lose Don't you want to win What is it
who is this
[laughter]
and how have you been lately
[music] I do
n't know who you think you are I
want you to act
smarter finish him just don't kill him
[music]
[applause]
get him off the Ring and give him to the people of
liang let them decide for themselves I don't care
[music]
I'm not here right now Tom If you wanted to
talk about something leave a
message If you hear any
interference please hang up carefully
[music]
fortunately we scared him with
this phone call on behalf of my
brother liang but if we don't
get out of here in time Bobby's people
will find us but for now here's what I'll tell you
Contact Helly she will help you survive
in the
jungle after I sort out
all the business I will find you
[music]
H
[applause]
[music]
with
[applause]
Hey you get out of your cotton wool go
your brother looks like he's got serious brain
damage help him up
here we go
[music] [music] [
music]
We're going in the right direction  let's go
miss where's your brother
[music]
[applause]
ur
[music]
[applause]
W
[music]
[applause] [music] [
applause] [
music] [music]
ah [applause] [
music] [applause] [
music]
[applause]
[music]
[applause] [
music] [applause] [
music] Oh [
music] [applause]
[music] [music] [
applause] [
music]
Give me that phone
[music]
[applause] [music
] [
applause] [music] [
applause] [
music]
[applause]
[music]
send your brother
look for brother
tsang tsang
where are you I can't see him from here
you should raise your head up
[music]
San get
off ah
[music] [music]
H Oh
[music] C [music]
ah
[applause] [
music] [applause] ah [
music]
[applause] [
music] [applause] [music]
brother [music] a [
music] [
music] a A [music]
[applause] [music]
H M
[applause]
what
ah
Non [
applause] [applause]
[music]
Oh
de
de Di ra
[applause] [music] [
applause] [
music]
no no no no
[music]
no a
Oh ra
[music]
not
[applause]
[music]
ah
[applause]
[music]
ah
[applause]
What the hell Can't you stop
them
[music]
ah
[applause]
[music]
[music] [
applause] [
music]
H
[music]
He
[applause]
[music]
Tai bye
Goodbye [music] So
in the jungle How do you
say Wild
fox Survival of
the fittest and you dare to deceive me like that
After using
my name Well you're on friendly
terms with Bobby Are
n't we used to be neither bitter enemies nor
friends We were just
gangsters But a few years ago
things got better between us
Sometimes he's
useful to me Maybe because
I did him a favor back in the day
What are you trying to say  you and him are on the same
side you seem a bit suspicious
why is this so will you help me or not
now I can't lend a helping hand
what is more important to you fame or
safety I don't want to get into a
conflict with Bobby now you have to decide all this yourself
I know but the reason I
came here
I want to stay in Chen forever not just
being a big brother what if the game is not
worth the candle but you know I'm not one of
those people that's comforting
another fight was arranged between
boxers Hu and Bobby everything depended on the
outcome of this fight you and many others
made your bets I acted
as a bookmaker so it was you
right Bob found out about it before
you a bet of 600,000 bucks to find out
which boxer is stronger the
security fee was not that
small but the benefit and keeping my
good name were more important to me that's
why I gave him my consent but Hu never made
so much money in my eyes
you are much more powerful than
him in our business we have to survive if you
remember this I know you are much more
reliable than the
others I can't do it alone  stand firm
but me and my friends can come to the rescue
as long as we can be useful to you after
what we've been through i'll call you
big sister
[music]
[applause]
don't worry i'll fight this
fight in place of big brother and for him
[music]
do throw down these gloves
second
brother i know what you're
thinking but don't answer me right
now i know what you're going to do
and why are you here wanting to fight these two
rounds instead of
san isn't it a bit early to judge
the situation the first one ut nan yu
[music] [music]
[applause] what does that
mean it's not me it's all your
stance i'm just showing you your
weaknesses but you can only judge by
who died and who survived
[music]
younger
brother this is the second time but i'm giving you
one last chance
if you're so arrogant you'll
soon end up
[laughter]
dead P
[music]
that's fair but i can be stronger than
his punch is 3 seconds faster
than
[music]
yours is the result of the difference in speed
[laughter]
heartbeat and
brain waves are normal but I
shouldn't hit him during the warm-up
shouldn't you counterattack after
his attacks He doesn't underestimate himself anymore
If you counterattack him from the
start He won't reach the desired
state his fighting potential is highly
dependent on the opponent
Don't focus on this better
think about your
actions
1.5
1.3.7
2.25 1.6
take advantage of his lag in
attacks Prepare all your muscles
Try to do everything as quickly as possible
avoid dangerous attacks to maintain
your normal state and ultimately
life Look at your
trainer
96 when he starts attacking more
furiously and you have to counterattack
so he doesn't touch you Use the
correct y to g urni
tom how best to dodge do it on
automatically if my punch is as
strong as now he will be
defeated they analyzed his basic
techniques with the help of a
computer let's look at his
personal
data so if he were a master of martial
arts and a boxer against him you can
use the terrain take him to
death alley maybe there is a way to
use his weaknesses against
him you could use a
computer to find his weak point
then you could easily defeat
him I want you to perform all your
punches at the very level and
counterattack from his attacks never
stop and show no mercy
don't let him enter a state of trance
as for the fourth level I
analyzed
you You can also do an attack in
deep
trance do everything like on other
levels but with less force But you will have
little strength left so you must
rebuild your body
When a series of his punches passes you will have to
gather all your strength and carry out a
crushing attack I will let you know when
it needs to be done Listen to the
gong strikes I will show you how it should be [
laughter]
[applause]
[music]
what are you  you
do It's a pity that the computer can't
show Which technique is better and who should be the
winner I'll show you now
We were taught the same thing The computer
says that he is a tiger but I think
differently
[music]
Ja [
music]
[applause]
Oh a ah ah a a [
applause
] [applause] a ah [laughter]
[music] a a a [music] [
laughter] [music]
a ah [music]
Go [music] [music] [
applause]
[music]
lonki Only you and me in this world
[applause]
translated and voiced by chesterfield
[music]
ga
mi ne Nuha
[music]
H
[music] [music] [music] [
music]
po [
go a
[music] [
music]
F
[music]
UN
BR
E E
[music]